

#### **Address**

Jaban, RT/RW 02/25, Sinduharjo Ngaglik, Sleman.

#### **Phone**

+62 8132 7348 203

#### Mail

nr.riandika@gmail.com

#### Site/GIT

nrriandika.github.io github.com/nrriandika

### **General Skills**



**GIS Analysis** 

**ArcGIS** QGIS MapInfo

#### Web GIS

Leaflet.js **PostgreSQL PostGIS** Geoserver

### Web Programming

HTML, CSS, JS PHP **Python Bootstrap** Laravel **GIT** 

# Novandi Resya Riandika

Geodetic Engineer - GIS Enthusiast

A Bachelor of Geodetic Engineering with expertise on GIS scope.

Extensive knowledge on data processing and analyzing including (GNSS, GIS, Remote Sensing, and 3D model data).

Highly qualified working as individual or team with well adaptability. Well-communicate person and familiar on leading a team.

## Education

2017 - 2019

Institut Teknologi Nasional Bandung

Bachelor's Degree in Geodetic Engineering

2014 - 2017

Universitas Gadjah Mada

Diploma in Geomatic Engineering

# Work Experience

2020 - now

GIS Developer

**Geospatial Information Agency** 

September - now

- Developing WebGIS for Pusat Batas Wilayah BIG.
- Create some new features for a better delivering spatial boundary data.

2020

March - October

Lead Surveyor

Spatial Department of Jogja

- Conduct GNSS Survey for evaluating the city boundary to create high quality boundary pillar.
- Establish new standard on city boundary regulation.

2019 - now

December - now

Research Assistant Komatsu & UGM

- Conduct series of GNSS quality assessment on new heavy equipment.
- Analyzing and reporting the GNSS quality assessment to help the company decision making.

2019

November - December

**Engineer Surveyor** 

CG Power Systems Id

- Conduct topography mapping on a newly open area to show a representative topography condition.
- Conduct design stakeout and leveling to create a wellplaned power-plant site.

2018

September - October

Internee

Badan Informasi Geospasial

Conduct a terrestrial gravity survey simulation.

2018

September - October

GIS Analyst | Spatial Information System Dept

Define new standard village mapping and it's boundary.

2015

September - October

GIS Analyst PT. Puri Green Resources

Conduct GIS Analysis, taken from UAV Rapid Mapping Data - very high resolution imagery for Oil Palm Estate.